<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<document>
	<public>
		<program name="Hero Lab" url="https://www.wolflair.com">
			<programinfo>Hero Lab and the Hero Lab logo are Registered Trademarks of LWD Technology, Inc. Free download at https://www.wolflair.com
Shadowrun © 2005-2019 The Topps Company, Inc. All rights reserved. Shadowrun is a registered trademark of The Topps Company, Inc.</programinfo>
			<version version="8.9h" primary="8" secondary="9" tertiary="h" build="958"/>
		</program>
		<localization language="eng" units="metric"/>
		<character active="yes" characterindex="1" nature="normal" role="npc" relationship="ally" type="Hero" name="Fred" playername="Brad Tallman">
			<race name="Basilisk"/>
			<heritage name=""/>
			<creation>
				<bp total="25" left="25"/>
			</creation>
			<karma total="7" left="7"/>
			<cash total="1000"/>
			<personal gender="Male" age="25" hair="" eyes="" skin="">
				<description/>
				<charheight text="1.75m" value="175"/>
				<charweight text="78kg" value="78"/>
			</personal>
			<defenses>
				<defense name="Ranged Defense" normal="6"/>
				<defense name="Melee Defense" normal="6"/>
			</defenses>
			<armorratings>
				<armorrating name="Armor" rating="7" stacking="7" nonstacking="0" dicepool="13"/>
				<armorrating name="Acid Protection" rating="7" stacking="7" nonstacking="0" dicepool="13"/>
				<armorrating name="Cold Protection" rating="7" stacking="7" nonstacking="0" dicepool="13"/>
				<armorrating name="Electricity Protection" rating="7" stacking="7" nonstacking="0" dicepool="13"/>
				<armorrating name="Fire Protection" rating="7" stacking="7" nonstacking="0" dicepool="13"/>
				<armorrating name="Falling Protection" rating="7" stacking="7" nonstacking="0" dicepool="13"/>
				<armorrating name="Fatigue Resistance" rating="0" stacking="0" nonstacking="0" dicepool="11"/>
			</armorratings>
			<attributes>
				<attribute name="Body" text="6" base="6" modified="6" naturalmaximum="9" augmentedmaximum="13" minimum="3" category="Physical">
					<description>Body measures your physical health and resiliency.

It affects how much damage you can take and stay on your feet, how well you resist damage coming your way, your ability to recover from poisons and diseases, and things of that nature.</description>
					<traitcost bp="6"/>
				</attribute>
				<attribute name="Agility" text="3" base="3" modified="3" naturalmaximum="6" augmentedmaximum="9" minimum="0" category="Physical">
					<description>Agility measures things like hand-eye coordination, flexibility, nimbleness, and balance. Agility is the most important attribute when it comes to scoring hits during combat, as you need to be coordinated to land your blows, whether you're swinging a sword or carefully aiming a rifle. It also is critical in non-combat situations, such as sneaking quietly past security guards or smoothly lifting a keycard from its secured position.</description>
					<traitcost bp="3"/>
				</attribute>
				<attribute name="Reaction" text="3" base="3" modified="3" naturalmaximum="6" augmentedmaximum="9" minimum="0" category="Physical">
					<description>Reaction is about reflexes, awareness, and your character's ability to respond to events happening around them. Reaction plays an important role in deciding how soon characters act in combat and how skilled they are in avoiding attacks from others. It also helps you make that quick turn down a narrow alley on your cycle to avoid the howling gangers on your tail</description>
					<traitcost bp="3"/>
				</attribute>
				<attribute name="Strength" text="7" base="7" modified="7" naturalmaximum="10" augmentedmaximum="15" minimum="4" category="Physical">
					<description>Strength is an indicator of, well, how strong your character is. The higher your strength, the more damage you'll do when you're raining blows down on an opponent, and the more you'll be able to move or carry when there's stuff that needs to be moved. Or carried.

Strength is also important with athletic tasks such as climbing, running, and swimming.</description>
					<traitcost bp="7"/>
				</attribute>
				<attribute name="Willpower" text="5" base="5" modified="5" naturalmaximum="8" augmentedmaximum="12" minimum="2" category="Mental">
					<description>Willpower is your character's desire to push through adversity, to resist the weariness of spellcasting, and to stay upright after being nailed in the head with a sap.

Whether you're testing yourself against a toxic wilderness or a pack of leather-clad orks with crowbars, Willpower will help you make it through.</description>
					<traitcost bp="5"/>
				</attribute>
				<attribute name="Logic" text="1" base="1" modified="1" naturalmaximum="4" augmentedmaximum="6" minimum="0" category="Mental">
					<description>The Logic attribute measures the cold, calculating power of your rational mind. Whether you are attempting to repair complicated machinery or patch up an injured teammate, Logic helps you get things right. Logic is also the attribute hermetic mages use to resist Drain from the spells they rain down on their hapless foes.

Deckers also find Logic extremely useful, as it helps them develop the attacks and counterattacks that are part of their online battles.</description>
					<traitcost bp="1"/>
				</attribute>
				<attribute name="Intuition" text="3" base="3" modified="3" naturalmaximum="6" augmentedmaximum="9" minimum="0" category="Mental">
					<description>Intuition is the voice of your gut, the instinct that tells you things before your logical brain can figure them out. Intuition helps you anticipate ambushes, notice that something is amiss or out of place, and stay on the trail of someone you're pursuing.</description>
					<traitcost bp="3"/>
				</attribute>
				<attribute name="Charisma" text="1" base="1" modified="1" naturalmaximum="4" augmentedmaximum="6" minimum="0" category="Mental">
					<description>Charisma is your force of personality, the persuasiveness and charm you can call on to get people to do what you want without having to go to the trouble of pulling a gun on them. It's not entirely about your appearance, but it's also not entirely not about your appearance. What it's mostly about is how you use what you have - your voice, your face, your words, and all the tools at your disposal - to charm and/or intimidate the people you encounter. Additionally, Charisma is an important attribute for shamanic mages, as it helps them resist the damaging Drain from spells they cast.</description>
					<traitcost bp="1"/>
				</attribute>
				<attribute name="Essence" text="6" base="6" modified="6" naturalmaximum="0" augmentedmaximum="6" minimum="0" category="Derived">
					<description>Essence is your metahumanity encapsulated in a number. In Shadowrun, you have ample opportunities to alter your body or push it beyond its normal limits. Such actions often have a cost, and they can result in a loss of a portion of your metahumanity, which means a loss of Essence points. Each character starts with an Essence rating of 6, and it acts as a cap on the amount of alterations you can adopt. When it's gone, it doesn't come back. It also affects the Magic and Resonance attributes, as losses in Essence are reflected by losses in Magic and Resonance.

While denizens of the Sixth World are accustomed to seeing a variety of augmentations and alterations to the metahuman form, the "uncanny valley" still exists. The uncanny valley is the disconcerting effect that happens when people see something that is almost, but not quite, metahuman. An animated cartoon with exaggerated features looks fine to metahuman eyes, but a computer program that closely, but not exactly, replicates human appearance is a troubling and unpleasant sight to most viewers. This is what happens when people see others with augmentations - on some level, people notice there is something less (or more) human about that, and they respond to it negatively. The change may not be exactly visible, but it is in some way noticeable - in one way or another, a person has become less human, and on some level other people notice this. This is why a character's Essence is included in the calculation of their Social limit.</description>
					<traitcost bp="6"/>
				</attribute>
				<attribute name="Edge" text="1" base="1" modified="1" naturalmaximum="4" augmentedmaximum="6" minimum="0" category="Special">
					<description>Edge is the ultimate intangible, that certain something that provides a boost when you need it, that gets you out of a tough spot when the chips are down. It's not used to calculate dice pools; instead, you spend a point of Edge to acquire a certain effect. Every character has at least one point of Edge, more if they want to take more frequent advantage of the boosts it offers. The possible effects of and more details about Edge are on p. 56.</description>
					<traitcost bp="1"/>
				</attribute>
				<attribute name="Magic" text="4" base="4" modified="4" naturalmaximum="7" augmentedmaximum="10" minimum="0" category="Heritage???Special">
					<description>If you intend to cast spells or use magic in any way, your character needs to have the Magic attribute. Most individuals do not have this attribute, meaning their rating is zero. Mages, who cast spells, and adepts, who channel magic into enhanced physical and mental abilities, need this quality. Their Magic rating measures how capable they are in the arcane arts and how much power they can draw down to help them in their efforts.</description>
					<traitcost bp="4"/>
				</attribute>
				<attribute name="Initiative" text="6+1D6" base="6" modified="6" naturalmaximum="12" augmentedmaximum="18" minimum="0" category="Derived">
					<description>Initiative governs how quickly a character responds in a combat situation. A character's Initiative attribute is their Reaction plus their Intuition.</description>
					<traitcost bp="0"/>
				</attribute>
			</attributes>
			<movementtypes>
				<movementtype name="Land Movement" sprintpool="9dicepool [8]">
					<walking text="3m" value="3"/>
					<running text="15m" value="15"/>
				</movementtype>
				<movementtype name="Swimming" sprintpool="15dicepool [8]">
					<walking text="10m" value="10"/>
					<running text="40m" value="40"/>
				</movementtype>
			</movementtypes>
			<reputations>
				<reputation name="Street Cred" value="0"/>
				<reputation name="Notoriety" value="0"/>
				<reputation name="Public Awareness" value="0"/>
				<reputation name="Astral Reputation" value="0"/>
			</reputations>
			<qualities>
				<positive/>
				<negative/>
			</qualities>
			<skills>
				<groups/>
				<active>
					<skill name="Perception" text="4" base="4" modified="4" naturalmaximum="12" augmentedmaximum="6" dicepool="7" group="">
						<description>Perception refers to the ability to spot anomalies in everyday situations, making it one of the key skills a shadowrunner needs. See Using Perception, p. 135.</description>
						<traitcost bp="0"/>
					</skill>
					<skill name="Running" text="2" base="2" modified="2" naturalmaximum="12" augmentedmaximum="3" dicepool="9" group="Athletics Group">
						<description>Running, as you may guess, is about how much ground you can cover quickly. For more information see Using Running, p. 136.</description>
						<traitcost bp="0"/>
					</skill>
					<skill name="Sneaking" text="3" base="3" modified="3" naturalmaximum="12" augmentedmaximum="5" dicepool="6" group="Stealth Group">
						<description>Need to get where you're not supposed to be? This skill allows you to remain inconspicuous in various situations. See Using Stealth Skills, p. 136.</description>
						<traitcost bp="0"/>
					</skill>
					<skill name="Swimming" text="8" base="8" modified="8" naturalmaximum="12" augmentedmaximum="12" dicepool="15" group="Athletics Group">
						<description>This skill determines the character's ability to swim in various bodies of water. The skill level affects the distance and speed at which a character can swim. See Using Swimming, p. 137</description>
						<traitcost bp="0"/>
					</skill>
					<skill name="Unarmed Combat" text="6" base="6" modified="6" naturalmaximum="12" augmentedmaximum="9" dicepool="9" group="Close Combat Group">
						<description>Unarmed Combat covers the various self-defense and attack moves that employ the body as a primary weapon. This includes a wide array of martial arts along with the use of cybernetic implant weaponry and the fighting styles that sprung up around those implants.</description>
						<traitcost bp="0"/>
					</skill>
				</active>
				<knowledge/>
				<language/>
			</skills>
			<gear>
				<augmentations>
					<cyberware/>
					<bioware/>
				</augmentations>
				<weapons>
					<item name="Bite" useradded="no" quantity="1" natural="yes">
						<description>Claws. Sharp, pointy teeth. A spiked tail. Whatever form it takes, the critter possesses some means of inflicting Physical damage. The description of this power describes the nature of the attack, as well as its Damage Value and Armor Penetration modifiers where applicable. Natural weapons may be either melee or ranged attacks, and critters follow standard combat rules when using them. Critters use the Unarmed Combat skill to attack with natural melee weapons, and the Exotic Ranged Weapon skill to attack with natural ranged weapons. Most natural weapons are considered normal weapons for purposes of the Immunity to Normal Weapons power; exceptions are noted in individual critter descriptions.

A dual-natured critter with a melee Natural Weapon can use this power against astral targets that are within its reach. Use the critter's normal Unarmed Combat skill and physical Damage Value for this attack. Ranged Natural Weapons, like other ranged combat, do not work on the astral plane. Critters without a Natural Weapon may still make an unarmed attack. As with regular characters, the Damage Value is (STR)S.</description>
						<gearcost text="0¥" value="0"/>
						<availability text="" value="0" class=""/>
						<matrix>
							<matrixattribute name="Attack" text="0" base="0" modified="0"/>
							<matrixattribute name="Sleaze" text="0" base="0" modified="0"/>
							<matrixattribute name="Data Processing" text="2" base="2" modified="2"/>
							<matrixattribute name="Firewall" text="2" base="2" modified="2"/>
						</matrix>
						<weaponinfo grouptext="Unarmed" dicepool="9dicepool [8]" damagetext="8P" damagevalue="8" damagetype="Physical" ap="-2" modestext="" isammunition="0" reach="" equipped="Main Hand">
							<defense name="Bite Parry" normal="6"/>
						</weaponinfo>
					</item>
				</weapons>
				<armor>
					<item name="Natural Armor" useradded="no" quantity="1">
						<description>Whether it comes in the form of dermal bone deposits, scales, or just a thick hide, a critter with this power has some inherent protection from physical attacks. The critter's natural Armor rating is cumulative with any armor worn.</description>
						<gearcost text="0¥" value="0"/>
						<availability text="" value="0" class=""/>
						<matrix>
							<matrixattribute name="Attack" text="0" base="0" modified="0"/>
							<matrixattribute name="Sleaze" text="0" base="0" modified="0"/>
							<matrixattribute name="Data Processing" text="2" base="2" modified="2"/>
							<matrixattribute name="Firewall" text="2" base="2" modified="2"/>
						</matrix>
						<armorinfo rating="+7" acid="0" cold="0" electricity="0" falling="0" fire="0" radiation="0" laser="0" equipped="yes" natural="yes"/>
					</item>
				</armor>
				<equipment/>
			</gear>
			<identities/>
			<contacts/>
			<ammotrackers/>
			<trackers>
				<tracker name="Cumulative Recoil" text="0" used="0" left="0" min="0" max="0"/>
				<tracker name="Edge Pool" text="0/1" used="0" left="1" min="0" max="1"/>
				<tracker name="Movement This Turn (Currently: Stationary)" text="0m" used="0" left="0" min="0" max="0"/>
			</trackers>
			<conditionmonitors totalpenalty="0">
				<conditionmonitor name="Physical Damage Track" boxes="11" penalty="0"/>
				<conditionmonitor name="Stun Damage Track" boxes="11" penalty="0"/>
			</conditionmonitors>
			<journals>
				<journal name="Title" gamedate="0" realdate="20200411" karma="0" cash="0" streetcred="0" notoriety="0" awareness="0">
					<description/>
				</journal>
			</journals>
			<images>
				<image filename="Critter NPC-image001.png"/>
			</images>
			<validation>
				<report/>
			</validation>
			<settings summary="Character Creation Systems: Established Runners; Character Creation Variants: Run Faster — Sum To Ten System; Core Rulebooks: Chrome Flesh, Data Trails, Howling Shadows, Rigger 5.0, Run &amp; Gun, Run Faster, Street Grimoire; Advanced Rules: Forbidden Arcana, Kill Code, Street Lethal; Supplements: Book of the Lost, Complete Trog, Cutting Aces, Dark Terrors, Hard Targets, Stolen Souls; E-books: Aetherology, Assassin's Primer, Bullets &amp; Bandages, Gun Heaven 3, Shadow Spells, Shadows in Focus: Metrópole, Shadows in Focus: San Francisco Metroplex; Optional Rules: Allow Adepts to Choose a Tradition, Allow Unlimited Negative Qualities; Optional Rules -&gt; Chrome Flesh Optional Rules: Gamma-Grade Cyberware, Omega-Grade Cyberware, Orks &amp; Trolls get natural weapons, Use Essence Holes; Optional Rules -&gt; Run &amp; Gun Optional Rules: RG2: Target Size Modifiers, RG3: Movement Penalties by Speed; Optional Rules -&gt; Street Grimoire Optional Rules: Reputation in the Spirit World; Output Options: Include Vehicle Statblocks on Sheet"/>
			<npc>
				<basics>
					<npcinfo name="Description">A metaspecies of the komodo dragon, the basilisk averages approximately 250 centimeters from its snout to the tip of its tail, and weighing around one hundred kilograms. They stand about twenty centimeters at the shoulder, are somewhat broader than their progenitor, and have a spiny dorsal fan, about thirty centimeters in height at its tallest point, running most of their length. Their scales are heavy; coloration is black and bright yellow, with a solid black snout and tail tip. Their maws are filled with sharp, saw-edged teeth that are constantly replaced as they're lost. Not surprisingly, they're aggressively carnivorous, typically feeding on fish and small mammals. They cheerfully glut themselves on anything they can catch, though, up to and including metahumans.

Extremely territorial, they are relatively easy to train and are used extensively as guard animals by a number of megacorps throughout the Sixth World.

Natural Habitat/Range: Native to Indonesia, basilisks can now be found in temperate and tropical woodlands worldwide. Powerful swimmers, their natural lairs are always near running water.</npcinfo>
				</basics>
				<tactics/>
				<ecology/>
				<additional/>
				<bookinfo name="CRB 403"/>
			</npc>
			<minions/>
		</character>
	</public>
</document>